[
    {
      "Timestamp": "8/14/2019 18:37:27",
      "Username": "LUL",
      "Question": "When will Flint MI have good water?",
      "QuestionPostDate": "9/1/2017",
      "QuestionPostTime": "9:56:00 AM",
      "QuestionAnswer": "Couple years",
      "AnswerPostDate": "10/1/2017",
      "AnswerPostTime": "10:55:00 AM"
    },
    {
      "Timestamp": "8/14/2019 18:38:13",
      "Username": "asljsdlfjk",
      "Question": "Lorem ipsum dolor sit amet, consectetur adipiscing elit, sed do eiusm",
      "QuestionPostDate": "7/2/2019",
      "QuestionPostTime": "5:18:00 AM",
      "QuestionAnswer": "veniam, quis nostrud exercitation ullamco laboris nisi ut aliquip ex ea commodo consequat. Duis aute iru",
      "AnswerPostDate": "6/22/2017",
      "AnswerPostTime": "3:34:00 AM"
    },
    {
      "Timestamp": "8/14/2019 18:39:18",
      "Username": "blight",
      "Question": "what happened to the dora?",
      "QuestionPostDate": "6/24/2019",
      "QuestionPostTime": "8:27:00 AM",
      "QuestionAnswer": "his new username is @blainesmagmar on some social media",
      "AnswerPostDate": "6/25/2019",
      "AnswerPostTime": "2:45:00 PM"
    },
    {
      "Timestamp": "8/14/2019 18:41:49",
      "Username": "thatonegamer",
      "Question": "how was your day?",
      "QuestionPostDate": "4/8/2018",
      "QuestionPostTime": "12:34:00 PM",
      "QuestionAnswer": "yes",
      "AnswerPostDate": "4/20/2019",
      "AnswerPostTime": "3:22:00 AM"
    },
    {
      "Timestamp": "8/14/2019 18:42:49",
      "Username": "Youngterp",
      "Question": "What day is in 2 days?",
      "QuestionPostDate": "4/14/2019",
      "QuestionPostTime": "3:00:00 AM",
      "QuestionAnswer": "24",
      "AnswerPostDate": "12/31/2018",
      "AnswerPostTime": "2:30:00 AM"
    },
    {
      "Timestamp": "8/14/2019 18:43:01",
      "Username": "Obby",
      "Question": "What's the square root of the out put of Blue times Red",
      "QuestionPostDate": "8/10/2019",
      "QuestionPostTime": "9:45:00 AM",
      "QuestionAnswer": "Bagel",
      "AnswerPostDate": "7/20/2019",
      "AnswerPostTime": "12:23:00 PM"
    },
    {
      "Timestamp": "8/14/2019 18:43:01",
      "Username": "Mario11243",
      "Question": "Favorite place to relax?",
      "QuestionPostDate": "4/8/2018",
      "QuestionPostTime": "11:42:00 PM",
      "QuestionAnswer": "Starbucks",
      "AnswerPostDate": "10/10/2018",
      "AnswerPostTime": "12:11:00 PM"
    },
    {
      "Timestamp": "8/14/2019 18:53:06",
      "Username": "TheWhiterOne",
      "Question": "Why is mental health only starting to gain importance in media now?",
      "QuestionPostDate": "8/14/2019",
      "QuestionPostTime": "10:00:00 AM",
      "QuestionAnswer": "I dont know. It should always have been talked about",
      "AnswerPostDate": "8/14/2019",
      "AnswerPostTime": "10:00:00 PM"
    },
    {
      "Timestamp": "8/14/2019 18:53:37",
      "Username": "Bob",
      "Question": "What is the velocity of a football thrown across 50 meters with 20 pounds of force?",
      "QuestionPostDate": "3/24/2019",
      "QuestionPostTime": "3:10:00 PM",
      "QuestionAnswer": "30mph/square foot",
      "AnswerPostDate": "5/16/2019",
      "AnswerPostTime": "4:43:00 PM"
    },
    {
      "Timestamp": "8/14/2019 18:54:35",
      "Username": "Smallboi",
      "Question": "Why do cowboys ride horses but not cows?",
      "QuestionPostDate": "7/27/2018",
      "QuestionPostTime": "2:20:00 AM",
      "QuestionAnswer": "I have no clue",
      "AnswerPostDate": "4/6/2019",
      "AnswerPostTime": "12:34:00 PM"
    },
    {
      "Timestamp": "8/14/2019 18:57:14",
      "Username": "AquaDragon82",
      "Question": "What is favorite type of weather?",
      "QuestionPostDate": "8/27/2019",
      "QuestionPostTime": "2:37:00 AM",
      "QuestionAnswer": "Rainy with no thunder clouds",
      "AnswerPostDate": "11/2/2019",
      "AnswerPostTime": "7:17:00 AM"
    },
    {
      "Timestamp": "8/14/2019 18:58:34",
      "Username": "scelerisque",
      "Question": "Lorem ipsum dolor sit amet, consectetur adipiscing elit, sed do eiusmod tempor incididunt ut labore et dolore magna aliqua.",
      "QuestionPostDate": "2/18/2019",
      "QuestionPostTime": "1:13:00 AM",
      "QuestionAnswer": "Vitae justo eget magna fermentum iaculis eu non diam phasellus.",
      "AnswerPostDate": "5/19/2019",
      "AnswerPostTime": "9:17:00 PM"
    },
    {
      "Timestamp": "8/14/2019 18:58:59",
      "Username": "SomeGuy29",
      "Question": "What is your least favorite animal?",
      "QuestionPostDate": "3/22/2017",
      "QuestionPostTime": "3:01:00 AM",
      "QuestionAnswer": "Pangolin",
      "AnswerPostDate": "1/9/2019",
      "AnswerPostTime": "2:12:00 PM"
    },
    {
      "Timestamp": "8/14/2019 19:00:28",
      "Username": "SomeDude77",
      "Question": "When you think of lava, what is the first thing you think of?",
      "QuestionPostDate": "4/16/2017",
      "QuestionPostTime": "9:59:00 AM",
      "QuestionAnswer": "It drips",
      "AnswerPostDate": "4/18/2017",
      "AnswerPostTime": "11:12:00 AM"
    },
    {
      "Timestamp": "8/14/2019 19:01:51",
      "Username": "SomeMale62",
      "Question": "Who’s a real cool kid?",
      "QuestionPostDate": "7/3/2019",
      "QuestionPostTime": "10:13:00 AM",
      "QuestionAnswer": "Twit",
      "AnswerPostDate": "7/3/2019",
      "AnswerPostTime": "5:32:00 PM"
    },
    {
      "Timestamp": "8/14/2019 19:01:57",
      "Username": "sed",
      "Question": "Viverra aliquet eget sit amet tellus cras adipiscing enim.",
      "QuestionPostDate": "12/18/2018",
      "QuestionPostTime": "4:00:00 PM",
      "QuestionAnswer": "Tempus iaculis urna id volutpat.",
      "AnswerPostDate": "12/19/2018",
      "AnswerPostTime": "11:11:00 PM"
    },
    {
      "Timestamp": "8/14/2019 19:03:57",
      "Username": "Vitae",
      "Question": "Suscipit adipiscing bibendum est ultricies. Sapien eget mi proin sed libero.",
      "QuestionPostDate": "1/13/2019",
      "QuestionPostTime": "3:12:00 AM",
      "QuestionAnswer": "Molestie at elementum eu facilisis.",
      "AnswerPostDate": "1/28/2019",
      "AnswerPostTime": "9:56:00 AM"
    },
    {
      "Timestamp": "8/14/2019 19:05:19",
      "Username": "nec",
      "Question": " Dui accumsan sit amet nulla facilisi morbi tempus iaculis urna. ",
      "QuestionPostDate": "12/30/2018",
      "QuestionPostTime": "2:59:00 AM",
      "QuestionAnswer": "Amet risus nullam eget felis eget nunc.",
      "AnswerPostDate": "1/1/2019",
      "AnswerPostTime": "7:00:00 PM"
    },
    {
      "Timestamp": "8/14/2019 19:06:35",
      "Username": "Odio",
      "Question": " Feugiat sed lectus vestibulum mattis ullamcorper velit sed.",
      "QuestionPostDate": "7/7/2019",
      "QuestionPostTime": "7:07:00 PM",
      "QuestionAnswer": "Sed viverra tellus in hac habitasse platea dictumst vestibulum rhoncus.",
      "AnswerPostDate": "8/8/2019",
      "AnswerPostTime": "10:10:00 AM"
    },
    {
      "Timestamp": "8/14/2019 19:07:59",
      "Username": "Cursus",
      "Question": "Turpis egestas pretium aenean pharetra magna.",
      "QuestionPostDate": "3/31/2019",
      "QuestionPostTime": "12:12:00 PM",
      "QuestionAnswer": " Arcu vitae elementum curabitur vitae nunc sed velit dignissim.",
      "AnswerPostDate": "4/5/2019",
      "AnswerPostTime": "3:08:00 PM"
    },
    {
      "Timestamp": "8/14/2019 19:26:34",
      "Username": "Mike",
      "Question": "Lul",
      "QuestionPostDate": "12/8/2019",
      "QuestionPostTime": "4:32:00 AM",
      "QuestionAnswer": "Gev ",
      "AnswerPostDate": "11/27/2019",
      "AnswerPostTime": "12:34:00 PM"
    },
    {
      "Timestamp": "8/14/2019 19:28:14",
      "Username": "MarshadowXD",
      "Question": "When is the last time you went to see a doctor?",
      "QuestionPostDate": "8/5/2019",
      "QuestionPostTime": "4:23:00 PM",
      "QuestionAnswer": "Last month.",
      "AnswerPostDate": "8/4/2019",
      "AnswerPostTime": "5:40:00 PM"
    },
    {
      "Timestamp": "8/14/2019 19:35:45",
      "Username": "Opera707",
      "Question": "Favourite Pokemon",
      "QuestionPostDate": "4/20/2019",
      "QuestionPostTime": "4:20:00 AM",
      "QuestionAnswer": "Is Weed a possible solution to world peace?",
      "AnswerPostDate": "4/20/2019",
      "AnswerPostTime": "4:20:00 PM"
    },
    {
      "Timestamp": "8/14/2019 19:45:07",
      "Username": "bruhgamer72",
      "Question": "Is a frog a person?",
      "QuestionPostDate": "6/21/2017",
      "QuestionPostTime": "7:51:00 PM",
      "QuestionAnswer": "It's a real kneeslapper.",
      "AnswerPostDate": "10/5/2018",
      "AnswerPostTime": "5:49:00 PM"
    },
    {
      "Timestamp": "8/14/2019 19:58:16",
      "Username": "DioSado",
      "Question": "How do you feel about the fast paced changes in society over the past two to three years?",
      "QuestionPostDate": "7/17/2019",
      "QuestionPostTime": "12:00:00 PM",
      "QuestionAnswer": "It's hard to grasp, so much is changed making it hard to adjust. Not to mention being belittled when you get it wrong. ",
      "AnswerPostDate": "8/1/2019",
      "AnswerPostTime": "5:23:00 AM"
    },
    {
      "Timestamp": "8/14/2019 20:10:04",
      "Username": "Zethanos",
      "Question": "What’s your favorite old school game?",
      "QuestionPostDate": "5/29/2019",
      "QuestionPostTime": "12:06:00 PM",
      "QuestionAnswer": "Ape Escape. ",
      "AnswerPostDate": "1/1/2019",
      "AnswerPostTime": "9:39:00 PM"
    },
    {
      "Timestamp": "8/14/2019 20:51:10",
      "Username": "Moonbeam",
      "Question": "How can someone find happiness?",
      "QuestionPostDate": "10/19/2017",
      "QuestionPostTime": "12:12:00 AM",
      "QuestionAnswer": "Could not answer",
      "AnswerPostDate": "10/25/2017",
      "AnswerPostTime": "12:15:00 AM"
    },
    {
      "Timestamp": "8/14/2019 21:28:26",
      "Username": "Bearstorm",
      "Question": "Why is Mac&Cheese so good?",
      "QuestionPostDate": "3/13/2019",
      "QuestionPostTime": "7:39:00 AM",
      "QuestionAnswer": "Great Dane ",
      "AnswerPostDate": "3/16/2019",
      "AnswerPostTime": "10:59:00 PM"
    },
    {
      "Timestamp": "8/15/2019 1:34:42",
      "Username": "fastduck",
      "Question": "how often do you see ducks",
      "QuestionPostDate": "11/23/2006",
      "QuestionPostTime": "11:44:00 PM",
      "QuestionAnswer": "alot",
      "AnswerPostDate": "6/18/2009",
      "AnswerPostTime": "1:25:00 AM"
    },
    {
      "Timestamp": "8/15/2019 2:06:51",
      "Username": "YeetGang",
      "Question": "Besides earth, what’s your favorite planet/exo planet/ dwarf planet in the universe",
      "QuestionPostDate": "7/14/2018",
      "QuestionPostTime": "5:05:00 AM",
      "QuestionAnswer": "Ceres",
      "AnswerPostDate": "9/10/2017",
      "AnswerPostTime": "3:01:00 AM"
    },
    {
      "Timestamp": "8/15/2019 2:53:39",
      "Username": "Jac",
      "Question": "Who inspired you as a kid the most?",
      "QuestionPostDate": "4/4/2018",
      "QuestionPostTime": "5:30:00 AM",
      "QuestionAnswer": "Bill Bowerman",
      "AnswerPostDate": "4/4/2018",
      "AnswerPostTime": "11:00:00 AM"
    },
    {
      "Timestamp": "8/15/2019 5:25:46",
      "Username": "Redhood312",
      "Question": "Do aliens exist?",
      "QuestionPostDate": "8/13/2019",
      "QuestionPostTime": "8:30:00 AM",
      "QuestionAnswer": "Possibly.",
      "AnswerPostDate": "8/14/2019",
      "AnswerPostTime": "7:00:00 AM"
    },
    {
      "Timestamp": "8/15/2019 7:14:14",
      "Username": "Adam b",
      "Question": "Why havent we been able to use time travel yet?",
      "QuestionPostDate": "8/15/2019",
      "QuestionPostTime": "10:12:00 AM",
      "QuestionAnswer": "Fainting penguins aren’t actually fainting, the name was given because as planes flew over they would look up and lose balance making them fall over.",
      "AnswerPostDate": "8/5/2019",
      "AnswerPostTime": "10:12:00 AM"
    },
    {
      "Timestamp": "8/16/2019 4:11:16",
      "Username": "Dwayne Ronson ",
      "Question": "Will San Andreas be the official end of California? ",
      "QuestionPostDate": "7/6/2019",
      "QuestionPostTime": "8:22:00 PM",
      "QuestionAnswer": "Many parts of California will be left in ruin. It will take many years for the Golden State to be rebuilt, however, the state’s physical and spiritual landscape will forever be altered by such devastation. ",
      "AnswerPostDate": "7/6/2019",
      "AnswerPostTime": "11:11:00 PM"
    },
    {
      "Timestamp": "8/16/2019 4:11:20",
      "Username": "Dwayne Ronson ",
      "Question": "Will San Andreas be the official end of California? ",
      "QuestionPostDate": "7/6/2019",
      "QuestionPostTime": "8:22:00 PM",
      "QuestionAnswer": "Many parts of California will be left in ruin. It will take many years for the Golden State to be rebuilt, however, the state’s physical and spiritual landscape will forever be altered by such devastation. ",
      "AnswerPostDate": "7/6/2019",
      "AnswerPostTime": "11:11:00 PM"
    },
    {
      "Timestamp": "8/16/2019 4:11:24",
      "Username": "Dwayne Ronson ",
      "Question": "Will San Andreas be the official end of California? ",
      "QuestionPostDate": "7/6/2019",
      "QuestionPostTime": "8:22:00 PM",
      "QuestionAnswer": "Many parts of California will be left in ruin. It will take many years for the Golden State to be rebuilt, however, the state’s physical and spiritual landscape will forever be altered by such devastation. ",
      "AnswerPostDate": "7/6/2019",
      "AnswerPostTime": "11:11:00 PM"
    },
    {
      "Timestamp": "8/16/2019 6:45:22",
      "Username": "VroomVroom",
      "Question": "Have you every traveled outside the US",
      "QuestionPostDate": "2/18/2018",
      "QuestionPostTime": "2:28:00 PM",
      "QuestionAnswer": "Yes",
      "AnswerPostDate": "2/19/2018",
      "AnswerPostTime": "2:02:00 AM"
    },
    {
      "Timestamp": "8/17/2019 8:12:57",
      "Username": "ZiggyCarrust",
      "Question": "how much would could a woodchuck chuck if a woodchuck could chuck wood",
      "QuestionPostDate": "4/20/2019",
      "QuestionPostTime": "7:49:00 AM",
      "QuestionAnswer": "forty-two",
      "AnswerPostDate": "6/9/2017",
      "AnswerPostTime": "4:59:00 PM"
    },
    {
      "Timestamp": "8/17/2019 8:13:54",
      "Username": "Ikwillyou",
      "Question": "Why Is Goku’s Hair turn Yellow",
      "QuestionPostDate": "12/19/2018",
      "QuestionPostTime": "3:34:00 PM",
      "QuestionAnswer": "Because In the manga it was just “no color”, because drawing in the black ink for Goku’s  Hair was annoying, but in the Anime, it was made Yellow.",
      "AnswerPostDate": "8/15/2019",
      "AnswerPostTime": "6:45:00 AM"
    },
    {
      "Timestamp": "8/17/2019 8:20:15",
      "Username": "ricosuave",
      "Question": "are dogs real?",
      "QuestionPostDate": "1/9/2019",
      "QuestionPostTime": "7:30:00 AM",
      "QuestionAnswer": "yes",
      "AnswerPostDate": "1/10/2019",
      "AnswerPostTime": "4:30:00 AM"
    },
    {
      "Timestamp": "8/17/2019 8:24:43",
      "Username": "twitistwitbackwards",
      "Question": "Hypothetically, how much nuclear material would I have to ingest to become the equivalent of a super mutant from Fallout? ",
      "QuestionPostDate": "11/7/2018",
      "QuestionPostTime": "4:20:00 AM",
      "QuestionAnswer": "Obligatory “not a nuclear scientist” here. However, I think you would probably die form ingesting any sort of nuclear/radioactive material. We can’t all become Strong from Fallout 4 unfortunately. ",
      "AnswerPostDate": "11/10/2018",
      "AnswerPostTime": "5:41:00 PM"
    },
    {
      "Timestamp": "8/17/2019 8:35:05",
      "Username": "DootDoot",
      "Question": "Can I legally own an octopus?",
      "QuestionPostDate": "3/25/2017",
      "QuestionPostTime": "3:50:00 PM",
      "QuestionAnswer": "You need to add more fiber in your diet",
      "AnswerPostDate": "5/4/2018",
      "AnswerPostTime": "1:37:00 AM"
    },
    {
      "Timestamp": "8/17/2019 8:54:23",
      "Username": "Excepteur",
      "Question": "Mi tempus imperdiet nulla malesuada pellentesque elit eget gravida cum?",
      "QuestionPostDate": "9/14/2018",
      "QuestionPostTime": "1:47:00 PM",
      "QuestionAnswer": "A cras semper auctor neque vitae tempus.",
      "AnswerPostDate": "11/6/2018",
      "AnswerPostTime": "2:13:00 PM"
    },
    {
      "Timestamp": "8/17/2019 8:54:29",
      "Username": "Excepteur",
      "Question": "Mi tempus imperdiet nulla malesuada pellentesque elit eget gravida cum?",
      "QuestionPostDate": "9/14/2018",
      "QuestionPostTime": "1:47:00 PM",
      "QuestionAnswer": "A cras semper auctor neque vitae tempus.",
      "AnswerPostDate": "11/6/2018",
      "AnswerPostTime": "2:13:00 PM"
    },
    {
      "Timestamp": "8/17/2019 8:55:28",
      "Username": "sem ",
      "Question": "Elementum curabitur vitae nunc sed?",
      "QuestionPostDate": "2/11/2019",
      "QuestionPostTime": "5:33:00 AM",
      "QuestionAnswer": "Et pharetra pharetra massa massa ultricies mi quis.",
      "AnswerPostDate": "7/1/2017",
      "AnswerPostTime": "9:48:00 AM"
    },
    {
      "Timestamp": "8/17/2019 8:56:21",
      "Username": "rhoncus ",
      "Question": " Est pellentesque elit ullamcorper dignissim cras tincidunt lobortis feugiat vivamus?",
      "QuestionPostDate": "3/27/2018",
      "QuestionPostTime": "11:11:00 AM",
      "QuestionAnswer": "Posuere lorem ipsum dolor sit amet.",
      "AnswerPostDate": "4/17/2019",
      "AnswerPostTime": "7:39:00 PM"
    }
   ]

